

## **Personnal skills**

- ✓ Strong interpersonal skills
- √ Teamworker
- ✓ Flexible and creative
- ✓ Efficient problem solver
- √ Project management
- $\checkmark$  Highly organised
- $\checkmark$  Outstanding attention-to-detail

#### **Tech Skills**

- √ Object-Oriented programming
- ✓ RESTful JSON APIs
- √ MVC (Model View Controller)
- √ Schema Design & PostgreSQL
- ✓ DB & ActiveRecord
- ✓ DOM Events & AJAX

# **Programming Languages**

- √ HTML5, CSS3
- √ JavaScript fundamentals
- √ Ruby on Rails

#### Languages

- ✓ French : Native
- √ English: Fluent
- ✓ Spanish: Intermediate

# Tools

- √ Visual Studio Code
- √ Bootstrap
- √ JavaScript Tools (Webpack, yarn)
- √ GitHub
- √ Slack
- √ Figma

#### Artistic skills

- √ Hand drawn art
- √ Tatoo design
- √ Mural mandal wall @poartry.by.pauline

### **LET'S CHAT**



0919-484-064



My portfolio



<u>paulinerouge@hotmail.com</u>



<u>paulinerouger</u>



paulinetw

# **Pauline Rouger**

# **Full Stack Developer**

#### **HERE'S MY STORY:**

Highly motivated Junior Developer seeking for a new professional adventure. I am a critical thinker with strong problem-solving skills with over 15 years' work experience in hospitality/travel industry. I am a fast learner and very adaptable, continually maintaining a positive attitude while interacting with my peers. I am constantly motivated to develop my skills and grow professionally: I am now looking to bring my upbeat and energetic personality as a team member and expand my knowledge in tech industry.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Founder & Travel Planner**

2019 - 2021

#### TIME TO TRAVEL | SINGAPORE

As a self-starter, I take proud to set myself challenging goals and self-motivate to success. Thanks to Time to Travel, I particularly developed my creativity and ingenuity; I developed my business idea and implemented it by participating in the development of my website, by searching for the right management and technical tools, and business strategies. This entrepreneurial adventure in Tourism in the wake of Covid, made me humble and resilient in the face of obstacles.

#### **Team Leader & Senior consultant**

2011-2020

#### HELLOWORLD | MELBOURNE & SINGAPORE

Managing a team of 25 people from 10+ nationalities, deepened my open-mindedness and improved my leadership skills. I learnt to communicate effectively and to be emotionally aware to better meet my team members' concerns. I collaborated proactively across all the group departments.

#### **Restaurant Manager**

WIRED CAFE | SAN DIEGO, USA PRIMADONNA | MONTREAL, CANADA 2007- 2010 2004- 2015

Hospitality management takes dedication and hardwork in a fast-paced environment. I flourished in my roles thanks to my efficiency and organisational skills. My ability to multi-task and general adaptability were also keys of my outstanding performance.

### **Reservation Agent**

2005-2007

#### PARTIR PAS CHER | ANGERS, FRANCE

Specialising in customer service, I would get out of my way to meet customers needs and solve complex situations. I built a strong relationship with my clients which helped the company to establish its customers` loyalty. Always taking the initiative to support struggling team members strengthened my ability to work in team.

# **EDUCATIONAL INFO**

# **Full-stack Web Developer bootcamp**

2021

#### LE WAGON, MELBOURNE (REMOTELY)

From the database to the user interface, learning HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, SQL, git, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on Rails.

### **Management Tourism Industry Bachelor**

2005

UNIVERSITY OF QUEBEC IN MONTREAL